<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>P2Enjoy Studio</title>
    <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio" />
    <updated>2022-07-17T11:12:32+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://p2enjoy.studio</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Disclaimer</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/disclaimer/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/disclaimer/</id>
            <category term="Legals"/>

        <updated>2022-07-16T17:49:23+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Disclaimer for P2Enjoy SAS and its published websites If you require any more information or have any questions about our&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h1>Disclaimer for P2Enjoy SAS and its published websites</h1>
<p>If you require any more information or have any questions about our site's disclaimer, please feel free to contact us by email at <a href="mailto:ceo@p2enjoy.studio" rel="nofollow">ceo@p2enjoy.studio</a>.</p>
<h2>Disclaimers</h2>
<p>All the information on this website or any other published website from the company - is published in good faith. P2Enjoy does not make any warranties about the completeness, reliability and accuracy of this information. Any action you take upon the information you find on any published website from the company, is strictly at your own risk. P2Enjoy will not be liable for any losses and/or damages in connection with the use of our website.</p>
<p>From our website, you can visit other websites by following hyperlinks to such external sites. While we strive to provide only quality links to useful and ethical websites, we have no control over the content and nature of these sites. These links to other websites do not imply a recommendation for all the content found on these sites. Site owners and content may change without notice and may occur before we have the opportunity to remove a link which may have gone 'bad'.</p>
<p>Please be also aware that when you leave our website, other sites may have different privacy policies and terms which are beyond our control. Please be sure to check the Privacy Policies of these sites as well as their "Terms of Service" before engaging in any business or uploading any information.</p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our disclaimer and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Update</h2>
<p>Should we update, amend or make any changes to this document, <a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/updates-and-notification-about-our-policies/" rel="nofollow">read how to be notified when it happens</a>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Updates and notification about our policies</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/updates-and-notification-about-our-policies/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/updates-and-notification-about-our-policies/</id>
            <category term="Legals"/>

        <updated>2022-07-16T18:00:47+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Read how to check the last update of our policies and how to notified of any changes occurs.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
<h2>Updates of our policy</h2>
<p>This website ans any other published website from the company is RSS ATOM compatible, you can easily subscribe to any page change via your web browser and being notified real-time of any updated content.</p>
<p>Every legal page have a last modification timestamp.</p>
<p>You're invited to go and subscribe to the feed of any legal page you want to be notified in the event of content change.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Notice on copyright and intellectual or industrial properties</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/notice-on-copyright-and-intellectual-or-industrial-properties/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/notice-on-copyright-and-intellectual-or-industrial-properties/</id>
            <category term="Legals"/>

        <updated>2022-07-16T18:00:32+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Retrouvez ici les méntions des contenus hébérgés et des leurs proprietaires.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Terms of sales</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/terms-of-sales/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/terms-of-sales/</id>
            <category term="Terms"/>
            <category term="Legals"/>

        <updated>2022-07-16T17:38:06+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Find here the Mandatory Consumer Information of the articles sold by the studio in accordance with its declaration of activity in the draft status of creation.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
<p>In order to use and take return or advantage of this website or any affiliate service we might use or provide, you must read and accept the <a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/terms-of-service/" rel="nofollow" style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Terms of service.</a></p>
<p>By pursuing the navigation or by subscribing to any affiliate service, you confirm you have read and accepted all the conditions and obligations.</p>
<h2>Internal policy</h2>
<p>As the company is not selling any service  by its own at the time of writing, there is not much to write here about.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">We intends to offers selling of digital goods in the near future</span>, please follow the page for future updates.</p>
<h2>External policy</h2>
<p>#P2Enjoy may use affiliated sites for some of its selling services like events organisations with ticket selling, fund risings, academics web binaries, NFT markets... and they might have a different terms of sales policy then our own.</p>
<p>We encourage you to read the terms of sales policy of any service we might recommend you via a link, a discussion on a social network, a mail... prior of using it to buy any product we sell through these platforms.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>We are the best, around🥋🧒</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/we-are-the-best-around/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/we-are-the-best-around/</id>
            <category term="About"/>

        <updated>2022-07-17T11:12:32+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    We are a passionate gaming studio who aim to help develop and promote fair, near-zero-carbon footprint and sustainable video-gaming on&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p data-key="11"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are a passionate gaming studio who </span><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">aim to help develop and promote fair, near-zero-carbon footprint and sustainable video-gaming</span></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> on the block-chain.</span></p>
<p data-key="32"><span data-key="31">We connect different talents to leverage the costs for every start-upper, <em>so you can focus on what you know you can do the best</em> 💯</span></p>
<p class="align-right" data-key="51"><span data-key="50"><strong data-slate-leaf="true">Why?</strong><em data-slate-leaf="true"> Because someone has to do that!</em></span></p>
<p class="align-left" data-key="53"><span data-key="52">Reach to us if you...</span></p>
<ol class="align-left" data-key="56">
<li data-key="55"><em><span data-key="52">dream to </span>work for the gaming industry 💭</em></li>
<li data-key="64"><span data-key="63">want to <em>help the planet breath anew </em>out of your success in the business 🌳</span></li>
<li data-key="68"><span data-key="67">like the block-chain ecosystem 🧱</span></li>
<li data-key="70"><span data-key="69">have a fun idea for a great game! 👾</span></li>
</ol>
<p class="align-left" data-key="62"><span data-key="61">We are eager to add you to the family if you're a illustrator 🎨, a game designer ⚙, a composer 🎼, a developer 👩‍💻👨‍💻 (either block-chain or front-end) and we will give you everything you need to achieve your dreams!</span></p>
<blockquote>
<p class="align-right">If you're interested in our story, <a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/p2enjoy-studio-history/">you can read an incipit here</a>.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our values:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/environment/" title="Read more about our environment engagement">Environment-friendly engagements of the studio and its projects.</a></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/shares/" title="Read more how we believe it is fair to share gaming earnings">Fair redistribution of the shares between the investors and the players </a>(no more Ponzi-like!).</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/fun/" title="Read more about our observations on current block-chain gaming">Games built for the long run: have fun for months!</a></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/actors/" title="Read more why we will prevail the local economy first over any one else">Give the local actors and the local economy the first lodge.</a></span></li>
</ul>
<address> </address><address><span style="color: #7e8c8d;">You can expand, by clicking on it, any of our value to have a better explanation of our vision and how we work to take those paths. </span></address>
<p><strong>Most importantly: w<span data-key="23">e want the block-chain gaming to be ecoresponsible and fun to ENJOY playing! Hence the #Enjoy in the #P2E 🥳</span></strong></p>
<p class="align-right">Because it's <strong>P</strong>(lay)<strong>2E</strong>(njoy).</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>OSTG</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/outerspace-~the-game~-/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/outerspace-~the-game~-/</id>
            <category term="The games"/>

        <updated>2022-07-12T19:28:59+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>P2Enjoy Studio</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/p2enjoy-studio/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/p2enjoy-studio/</id>
            <category term="The studios"/>

        <updated>2022-07-12T19:21:51+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Cookie policy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/cookie-policy/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/cookie-policy/</id>
            <category term="Legals"/>

        <updated>2022-07-16T17:29:06+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://p2enjoy.studio/media/posts/14/mockaroon-bzLhhI3MpYY-unsplash.jpg" alt="Not a bunch of cookies" />
                    <p>Find here the general conditions of use about any of ours website relating to the use of cookies.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://p2enjoy.studio/media/posts/14/mockaroon-bzLhhI3MpYY-unsplash.jpg" alt="Not a bunch of cookies" />
                
<p>In order to use and take return or advantage of this website or any affiliate service we might use or provide, you must read and accept the <a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/terms-of-service/" rel="nofollow" style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Terms of service.</a></p>
<p>By pursuing the navigation or by subscribing to any affiliate service, you confirm you have read and accepted all the conditions and obligations.</p>
<h2>Internal policy</h2>
<p><strong>#P2Enjoy</strong> is a blockchain company and, just like you, we care about privacy: our own and yours.</p>
<p>The featured image of the page is called "not a bunch of cookies 🍪" (they are <em>macarons</em>, it's a pastry from France that you should absolutely try once in a lifetime) because we choose to not use any cookie for our websites: so there is not much more to say here.</p>
<p>We still collect some analytics via publicly available data, you can read more about what and how and when and if data is collected <a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/privacy-policy/" rel="nofollow">here</a>.</p>
<h2>External policy</h2>
<p>#P2Enjoy may use affiliated sites for some of its services like events organisations, ticket selling, fund risings, web binaries, podcasts, social networks... and they might have a different cookie policy then our own.</p>
<p>We <strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">DO NOT</span></strong> exploit the cookies (if any) from any service we might be partnering or working or sub-contracting part of our business.</p>
<p>Since we care for your privacy, we encourage you to read the cookie policy of any service we might recommend you via a link, a discussion on a social network, a mail... prior of using it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Privacy policy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/privacy-policy/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/privacy-policy/</id>
            <category term="Legals"/>

        <updated>2022-07-16T17:28:17+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Find here the terms and conditions of use of the data collected by this and any other website published or owned by the company.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
<p>In order to use and take return or advantage of this website or any affiliate service we might use or provide, you must read and accept the <a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/terms-of-service/" rel="nofollow" style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Terms of service.</a></p>
<p>By pursuing the navigation or by subscribing to any affiliate service, you confirm you have read and accepted all the conditions and obligations.</p>
<h2>The general policy</h2>
<p>#P2Enjoy is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities.<br><br>To provide you with the best experience possible while using the Website, upon purchase of products from this company, upon interaction with support services, upon subscribing for any organised event and other marketing and other interactions between you and any other of our affiliates service, you may from time to time provide some personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”).<br><br>#P2Enjoy is committed to collect and process Personal Data only in accordance with its rights and responsibilities under the applicable laws and regulations, including the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).</p>
<p>In order to performs its operations with (not exthensive list of) customers, contractors, subscribers, business partnership and alike; #P2Enjoy might process personal data during the process of doing.</p>
<h2>Analytics of the sites published by the company</h2>
<p>#P2Enjoy use <a href="https://umami.is/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Umami</a> for its analytics on theirs published websites.</p>
<p>Umami does not collect any personally identifiable information and all data collected is anonymous. Users cannot be identified and are never tracked across websites. All data is stored as aggregated statistics only.</p>
<p>The statistics being aggregated and stored are:</p>
<ul>
<li>counters for each visited pages</li>
<li>counters for visitors page referrers</li>
<li>counter for name and version of the browser of the visitors used to navigate the site</li>
<li>counter for name and version of the operating system of the visitors</li>
<li>counters for each generic class of the device being used by the visitor like desktop pc, mobile phone, tablet...</li>
<li>counters for the country of the visitors: no city, no region, no street... only the country.</li>
</ul>
<p>Statistical data is retained for as long as the referred service is available on-line and it's deleted once the service target of the analytics goes off-line.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Terms of use</title>
        <author>
            <name>Martino BETTUCCI</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://p2enjoy.studio/terms-of-usage/"/>
        <id>https://p2enjoy.studio/terms-of-usage/</id>
            <category term="Terms"/>
            <category term="Legals"/>

        <updated>2022-07-16T17:21:31+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Find here the TCU relating to the services offered by the studio via its websites.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
<p>In order to use and take return or advantage of this website or any affiliate service we might use or provide, you must read and accept the <a href="https://p2enjoy.studio/terms-of-service/" rel="nofollow" style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Terms of service.</a></p>
<p>By pursuing the navigation or by subscribing to any affiliate service, you confirm you have read and accepted all the conditions and obligations.</p>
<h2>Origins of the users</h2>
<p>The <span style="text-decoration: underline;">full extent</span> of the services offered by the company and its games or affiliates are available to EU citizen only.</p>
<p>If you subscribe or buy or get in any business relationship with the company and you are not a EU citizen, you understand that some services or service behaviours might not be offered to you and some services might behave differently based on your region or state of residence.</p>
<p>The order of unavailable services or changed behaviours for non-EU citizens will be stated on the page of the service itself.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
